This time, the project is "Earphone Gun Gun Shopping"!
Each participant will put on an earphone in Bakugon and tell what he/she wants to buy at the convenience store by playing a message game!
If they successfully get the item they want, the game is over!
Hello everyone!
This is Realy Calls Noise!
This time, for the first time in a while, we're going to do a YouTube-like project.
We're going to play a game where we tell people what we want them to buy at a convenience store with their earphones in.
There are 4 of us, so we will play 4 rounds!
How about it? How many times will you try? Do you think you can succeed?
It's been about a year since we formed.
Two or three times?
Three times?
We can do it!
Fourth time! Our goal is high!
I'd like to do it!
I don't see Alice moving her mouth too much.
I'm going to try a little harder to read Alice's mind!
I'll do my best!
Then let's do our best!
I will read Alice's mind!
I'd like to announce the topic!
Oronamin C and Chocola BB Royal 2!
Okay, then, let's do it!
May I?
Oronamin C
Oronamin C and Chocola, two.
Chocola, BB.
Royal Two.
Hmm?
Chocola, BB
Mm-hmm.
Royal Two.
Hm?
I'm sorry about the next word.
What?
Alice, the angel is sleeping.
Sleeping angel.
That's cute.
I'll go with the first one.
Maybe the first one.
Barley.
Good, good, good.
Second one.
Two. Two.
small
and
what, what, what?
You don't seem to know.
Do you think that's enough?
I think we're done here.
What is it?
only, only, only!
What?
Second one... and the second one... say it again.
The second one.
small
na
B B
Ear?
B B D
B B
Ear?
B
Next.
Wake me up from my slumber.
I have no idea what's going on.
Ah!
There are two.
Two?
Omugi.
I don't care.
Diaper.
That's a lot!
I believe in Alice.
Yeah.
dj, look at you.
neana Tapacchan, you're old, graves, aumentar
I'll take mine.
I should have done it with my hands.
Okay? I'll just do one round then.
Okay, okay.
Oronamnesty.
And...
Here.
beautiful
Roads and Yaobutsu
Okay, okay.
What? You really got it, didn't you?
I got it.
Russia.
O-ro-nin.
Three, two, one, shh.
Zawa imi?Zawaimi?
I'm going to change it in Panima.
That's what I meant.
The second one.
I'll change it with Panima.
We're done.
Yah!
Second one.
You definitely didn't get the message.
Oh, no.
What's the subject?
Can I go?
Jagarico, L-size, salad flavor.
Bon appétit!
Jagarico, size L, salad flavor.
Jagarico, salad flavor.
Jagariko, grilled.
Jagariko
Yale size salad flavor
Sashimi?
That's crazy.
Jagarico
Baked sweet potato?
It sure looks like it.
I don't know what to do!
But I think he said something about a baked potato.
Ya...
Hmm?
Big!
Oh, my God.
Yes, sir.
.......................
more
arrow (mark or symbol)
Pacific oyster (Crassostrea gigas)
tree
sea bream (Sparidae)
(bowing and) greeting
cloud
greatness and smallness
title
the reigns (i.e. of an emperor, emperor of a kingdom, etc.)
(after a noun) used when calling out to someone
(after a noun) relying on the verb "dai" or "dai" as its adjective
the ......................
The End?
The end?
It's over.
The managers are laughing so hard.
They're laughing so hard.
Who was scared of this?
How long has this been going on?
Next time...
My subject.
Widerin multivitamins.
Hardly.
Widder.
Widder
Wider
w
wider
da
Ui Dai Jyu Ri
Ui Daian Jyuri
Oui dai yu ri
great great great
Ui
great
great great
Uyida
Uyeda
printer
Printer?
Not a printer. Beer.
Uin-Uin.
Uyan.
Uiya.
I bet you're a beer drinker.
Jelly.
Zeli.
What? What? Huh?
One more time, one more time.
Zeli.
What? You've been chewing on it all day.
Just keep on smooching.
Zeli.
Pudding cake!
Ehhhh...
Kekke, I believe in BOJIMU
Pudding cake Pudding cake Pudding cake
pudding cake pudding
pudding cake
pudding cake pudding kekke
Watch again!
The answer is Giant Caprico and Milk Chalamel!
Giant Caprico
Caprico.
Giant...Giant...
Giant
From the beginning to the beginning
Giant Caprico.
Caprico somehow.
Giant...
........................
Giant Caprico... - Giant Caprico...
One more time, one more time.
Punyo
Punto...
What's that, Caprico? Giant?
AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!
And there's one more.
Milk caramel.
One more.
Caramel
Nakameguro
Eh, one more time.
Caramel
Milk Caramel
Giant Caprico and Milk Caramel
Eh, I can't hear you.
Ohhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! ahhhhh ahhh ahhh ahhh ahhh ahhh ahhh ahhh ahhh ahhh ahhh ahhh ahhh ahhh ahhh ahhh ahhh
One more time
Gian and
Caprico
With Gian and
Jaguarico
Gian and Caprico
Shampoo
Caprico
Something and Caprico
Shampoo and Caprico
Give up once, take another
One more
Milk
Water
Caramel
Caramel Milk caramel
One more milk caramel, one more water caramel, one more milk caramel
Caprico Leave Caprico out.
Milk caramel
Caprico Caramel
From the beginning
Giant Caprico and Milk Caramel
Milk caramel and syrup.
Okay, that's it.
Yes, that's okay.
Syrup.
Caprico. - Caprico.
Caprico.
Caprico
Caprico?
Shampoo
Jump?
Shampoo.
Like Weekly Shonen Jump.
Candy, shampoo, and jagarico.
Jagarico.
Jagarico
Jugarico with syrup and...
What was it?
Shampoo. Shampoo.
The products I want you to buy for me are... barley and oozawami.
I don't have any close by, Ai. I'll tell you the correct answer.
The first one was Oronamichi and Chocola BB Royal 2.
It's a big mistake, the first one was a disaster
Chocola BB was lent to me by Emi Ozawa! Sorry, Ai!
Then the second round, the subject Connor wanted me to buy for him...
I won! It was a big, big, big fail!
Daikon Salad
Conner-chan wanted me to buy her a daikon salad, please!
The correct answer is "Jagaico L-size salad"!
What part of "large"?
It's so abbreviated.
What did Alice say?
"Large.
It was right on.
Then it almost worked.
Next.
What did you think Aoi wanted me to buy her?
Pudding cake.
What I wanted her to get me?
Widerin multivitamins.
Multivitamin?
But Alice is a real piece of work.
That was really awesome.
That's great.
That's totally me.It wasn't me at all.
But I was good in the beginning.
Up until Widder.
You did? Me?
I was running fast in the middle of the race, too.
That was me.
Last question.
What did you think Alice wanted me to buy her?
Taffy.
Shampoo
Jagariko (potato chips)
Caprico
That's great!
You remember lying.
That's great.
Okay, Alice, give me the correct answer.
The correct answers are Giant Caprico and Milky Challah Mel.
I knew it.
I was right.
I was chewing on some milk.
I had him sharpen it right here.
Milk.
I ignored what I could get through, and I went for it.
So all four rounds failed.
What's going on?
We've been together for a year.
But the wounds are too deep.
Let's try to read their minds.
Okay.
So this time, I did some earphone shopping!
If you like this video, please click the "Good" button and subscribe to our channel!
That's all for now, Nearly Call Joy!
Bye bye!